{
    "subject": "resource/Sarah_Kennedy",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/West_Sussex",
    "human_readable": "Sarah Kennedy was born in West Sussex.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8391932249069214,
            "question": "Where was Sarah Kennedy born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7842388153076172,
            "question": "In what county was Sarah Kennedy born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40049317479133606,
            "question": "What is Sarah Kennedy known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35076069831848145,
            "question": "Where might Sarah Kennedy reside currently?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29345396161079407,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Sarah Kennedy's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24469618499279022,
            "question": "What is Sarah Kennedy's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22107824683189392,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Sarah Kennedy's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.210855171084404,
            "question": "Are there any public records related to Sarah Kennedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18418368697166443,
            "question": "Has Sarah Kennedy achieved any notable accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16313423216342926,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Sarah Kennedy's education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sarah Kennedy was born in West Sussex.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8652_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Sarah Kennedy achieved any notable accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8652_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any public records related to Sarah Kennedy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8652_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Sarah Kennedy's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8652_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8652_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Sarah Kennedy was born in West Sussex."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Sarah Kennedy was born in Coquille, Oregon, USA, not West Sussex.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There are multiple sources stating she was born in East Grinstead, Sussex.  Additionally, one source states her birthdate as July 8, 1950, not January 27, 1948.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that Sarah Kennedy was born in Sussex (specifically East Grinstead) and on January 27, 1948. Additionally, the information provided about her birthplace being West Sussex contradicts the given date of birth as well as other biographical details that place her birth in England, not the United States.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}